Mayank Singhal

Mayank, Btech CSE student at Manipal University Jaipur, excels in community engagement, event management, and graphic design. Deputy Head of Events and Head of Graphic Designing at MUJ ACM SIGBED. Expert in event organization, teamwork, and social media management. LaVisuals Discord owner, achieving 30% revenue growth. Ujjwal Gamer Discord moderator, known for online events and tournaments. Ready for impactful opportunities.



Experience

LaVisuals Discord (Feb, 2021 - Present)

Key Responsibilities as Founder/Owner

- Developed and launched a thriving online marketplace, offering premium anime graphics to customers
- Spearheaded effective customer engagement and business development efforts, resulting in an impressive revenue growth of 30%
- Fostered skill development and retention rates of over 90% through engaging and interactive training programs
- Successfully delivered workshops and bootcamps to groups of 25+ participants

MUJ ACM Sigbed Chapter (Feb, 2023 - April, 2024)

Key Responsibilities as Head of Graphic Designing

- Created impactful event posters, standee designs, and promotional materials, amplifying event visibility and attendance.
- Designed captivating Instagram reels, event videos, and ID cards, enhancing Sigbed's online presence and boosting traction.

MUJ ACM Sigbed Chapter (Feb, 2023 - April, 2024)

Key Responsibilities as Deputy Head of Events

- Facilitated track-making for Robo Soccer and moderated Circuitrix Event, fostering teamwork and engagement, ensuring seamless execution, and garnering positive eedback
- Amplified event participation through strategic planning and execution, resulting in increased attendance and aggement.

Education

Manipal University Jaipur (Sep, 2022)
Grade 8.33/10 CGPA

Lovely Public Sr. Sec. School (2022 Science Stream 93.3%

Lovely Public Sr. Sec. School (2020)
High School 92.3%

Strengths

Skils

- Event Moderation
- Community Building
- Team Leadership
- Graphic Designing
- Public Engagement
- Business DevelopmentStrategic Thinking

Softwares

- Figma
- Adobe After effects
- Adobe Photoshop
- Final Cut Pro
- Cinema4D
- Blender